what's up everybody in this video I'm
going to give you the very best products
to sell online in 2024 now I have to
warn you most of you are not going to
make six figures after you watch this
video and it's because I believe that
most people just aren't cut out for
business but I'll tell you this if you
watch to the end I'm going to get you as
close as possible to making the decision
of what the very best product are to
start and my goal is this to help you
decide do I want to stay in a corporate
job work for somebody else and struggle
or do I want to start my own business
and learn how to make 10,000 20,000
$30,000 a month working 10 to 15 hours a
week my name is jerem Kowski and for the
last 21 years I've been in the online
marketing and sales space selling
digital products info products CDs DVDs
seminars Ecommerce You Name It We have
done it successfully mind you we built
multiple companies over $20 million per
year in profit and listen don't let that
scare you way to think that I don't know
what it takes for a beginner to start in
fact that's what I have dedicated my
life to doing is helping people get
started from ground zero to be able to
build a success uccessful business now
I'll tell you this just a just a little
bit as well maybe you might not think
that it's possible for you maybe maybe
you've only ever worked a corporate job
for me personally I I'll tell you I tell
tell you that whole story I was working
in corporate jobs for the longest time
helping entrepreneurs build their
businesses to over $20 million a year
and and and I'm not going to bore you
with all the details of that but I had a
mindset that prevented me from building
my own business business successfully
and I'm and I'm excited to share that
last year we did $1.2 million in our
business we got a seven figure business
and I haven't made less than a quarter
of a million dollars a year since 2011 I
had one period where I I made less than
that back in 2009 and 2010 for about two
years but since then that's 13 years now
I haven't made less than a quar million
dollars a year and so I know exactly
what it takes to make that much money
consistently in my sleep roll out of bed
barely coherent and I can tell you the
few key things to do and we've done so
in this space the digital marketing info
product online sales space okay so you
might be hearing a few words that maybe
you don't like sales right we don't we
we're like H I don't want to sell well
how do you expect to make money online
so you got to address that first off
right I'm just going to come right out
the gate and kind of rip the Band-Aid
off a little bit sales is a requirement
you need to become what I call a trained
sales assassin and and and again what
this means is being able to laser in
like a sniper on exactly the market that
is going to make you the most amount of
cash one of the number one things that I
tell people is this your main priority
needs to
be cash flow
okay what is going to bring in maximum
profit as far as this
goes and this is where most people can't
go because they're way too focused on
all the other stuff as to why they they
don't want to focus on the money as far
as this goes you will not be able to
have a business if you don't focus on
profit and money okay there's you can
have a charity you can have a
nonprofit you can have a hobby that is
fulfilling and makes you feel happy but
you're not going to learn a lot of that
from me you're going to learn a lot of
the tactics and strategies that actually
bring in cash flow okay and so if you
don't want to bring
in five to let's just let's just let's
just round it up to
$225,000 per month right that's a that's
a pretty decent an income for most
people where you have options depending
on where you want to live as far as this
goes if you want to live in a city like
Austin Texas where I live right now and
you want to be able to buy a home here
and have a comfortable life you got to
be making right around that that uh 15
to
25,000 a month level right here minimum
to be able to do that but but if you
want to live maybe somewhere that's a
little bit more rural you can you can be
right at about 5 to 10,000 and have the
same quality of life as you might in
Austin Texas at this it's just different
different economies different different
parts of parts of the country Austin's
pretty expensive I love it here it's
amazing it's an incredible City if you
have an opportunity to visit please do
so highly encourage it you might just
want to move here the energy here is
electric and that's why I love it here
I've actually lived here I moved away
and then moved back with my wife back in
2018 and I I don't think I'm ever going
to leave this area it's just it's just
incredible we're planting Roots here
we're we're we're building growing our
family we just bought a home last year
my my son where we have another baby on
the way listen I'm all in on Austin
Texas as far as that goes and it's cool
because it's a different part of Texas
it's like a little it's like if you took
some of the great parts of
California and dropped them in the
middle of Texas and then you got all the
great parts of Texas and they melted
together that's Austin and I think I
think that that's pretty cool it's like
a nice uh it's like the best parts of
two polar opposite I would say
California Texas polar opposite uh
cultures and then you merge them
together with all their best parts
that's why I love Austin it really is
one of the best cities but you didn't
come here to hear about Austin I just
I'm a big fan of it as far as as you can
tell what I want to tell you is this is
that for you to be able to make the kind
of money that you want to make so that
you don't have to work for somebody
else you got to prioritize cash flow now
what is going to bring in cash flow for
you well the only way that you're going
to make that much money in your own
business is you have to
provide value
okay now here's here's the thing I I
just want to say this if you've been in
the space for a while you've been trying
to learn stuff online you know that the
marketplace for Value the problem is
value alone isn't going to make you a
dime and I'm might be one of the first
people to tell you
that okay you have to combine
Value
Plus
skills okay and what are the skills the
skills to pay the bill well you know
that sounds funny but it is it's the
skills that bring in the cash flow so
just providing value alone there's a lot
of people that give away
value but they don't have the skill set
to turn value into cash flow and that my
friends is a bit more of a challenge as
far as that goes so right away you have
to decide that I'm going to learn the
skills that it takes to provide value
and and that's exactly what I do that's
exactly what we do over at my website
Jeremiah Kowski decom is we teach you we
Mentor you both through my
podcast um we got tons of episodes in
our podcast right here you can check it
out the grow Your Life podcast it's like
a coach in a box where I walk you
through lots of aspects in building your
business beating writers block choosing
the right software platforms uh boosting
your productivity landing pages
persistence selling by letting go of the
sale this one right here will make you a
ton of money as far as that goes but all
that to say learning the skills on what
it takes to be able to sell the value
that is what you need to know so whether
you're doing e-commerce if you're
selling a physical product where do we
find the products how do we get the
manufactured how do we then get people
to buy it how do they find our product
or you're creating an info product such
as a course or a membership or a
subscription how do you create something
that is of value that's the easy part by
the
way some of you are like wait a sec what
that's the easy part it is because I
meet a ton of people I do they watch
these videos they have value but they
have no skill when it comes to selling
it and they don't know how to sell and
they don't know how to turn the value
into sales so if you want to answer this
question of what is the best products to
sell online right now I'm going to tell
you this it's what creates
consistency in your life and when we
talk about consistency it's what can you
count on and rely on that's going to be
there for you week after week after week
because right now we live in a time
where there is uncertainty okay look at
the world around you we don't know what
next week might hold let alone next year
and so creating consistency in your life
and in your business is what I believe
everybody needs to do and that starts by
packaging your value into what I call a
subscription offer
okay where people
pay
monthly for what you had to offer and
some of you might be like well I don't
want to lock people into a monthly
payment or something like that right n
none of us really like having another
subscription as far as this goes but can
I tell you this subscription models are
what make business
grow in 2024 we have to really balance
the fact of what we maybe don't like
about the world around us and what
actually works how many of y'all don't
want to have another Netflix or another
Disney Plus or a Hulu or things like
that right can I tell you this those
companies though make more
money selling subscriptions and there's
a reason why companies sell
subscriptions more than anything else
what I love to teach people is this is
how to do a low ticket subscription you
could go as low as $7 a
month seven
bucks or some of our clients have as
high
as 2 $1,000 a month as far as this goes
that we've worked with now that's a big
range right $7 a month $22,000 a month
what in the world would somebody pay
$2,000 a month for well I'll tell you
exactly what it is I'm going to show you
one of our clients that we've worked
with for for a while is over here at a
real change.com
and it's a VIP stock program called the
VIP up level program if you scroll right
down right here $22,000 a month and what
it is is it's mentoring that includes an
academy on trading stocks real time
Market updates strategy sessions market
analysis all of this combined together
in a community that will help people be
able to learn how to trade stocks but go
beyond just the basics of learning how
to trade how to have access to the best
information right away as as far as that
goes okay so but what this is
essentially is if we break it down it's
an information coaching program it's a
VIP membership mentorship program and
and and this client has I believe a few
hundred people in this program right
here at this level $2,000 a month okay
they also have a level that is
$177 a month they have a few thousand
people at that level now that's a very
successful highly profitable business as
far as that goes maybe you're watching
this right now and you're like okay few
hundred few thousand people gosh I'd be
happy if I just had 20 people that's
exactly don't neglect Small Beginnings
and I think that that's a good mindset
to have is how do we get
you to get and and let's let's shrink
this down right here I think this is a
really great goal for you
is your
first
20 sales
okay because that makes it tangible it
makes it something that is doable it
makes it something that we can really
look back at and say okay I can make
that happen I can get 20 people to give
me seven
bucks now that's not going to make you
rich right but that's
$140 a month that you didn't have as far
as that goes okay and and and and here's
what I found is that whether you're
making a million dollars a month or
you're bringing in a $100 a month the
strategies are the same once you get to
where you're
making 200 500
1,000 $22,000 a month
consistently by the way most people
don't even know how to do
that you figured out something that 99%
of people don't know how to do and then
what you got to do is you have to then
start scaling and a lot of people are
looking to scale way
sooner than even just validating and
getting an initial test going and
experimenting some things so what I
encourage people to do is I encourage
you to adopt what is is called an
experimentation
mindset
okay and we have to have a growth
mindset when we think about all of these
things what is the difference between a
growth and a fixed mindset a fixed
mindset says how I've always done things
is is how it's always going to be and
that's just how I am that's my
personality I can't grow I can't change
I have evidence in my life and the
people that I've worked with to see
people that are not qualified I can tell
you right now me
personally I was qualified for years to
not be the guy who was in front of the
camera teaching selling mentoring people
and if I look back even at my life and
the mistakes that I've made back when I
struggled with alcohol drinking hanging
out with friends that were not healthy
for me as far as that goes I was not in
a position I to do anything but help
somebody else make a lot of money and I
had to reinvent myself and create a
brand new life to where I wasn't
manipulated by other people to where I
didn't let other people's opinions of me
stop me to where I didn't become afraid
of people disliking me people's
disapproval as far as that goes and
maybe you're listening to me right now
and you're like well Jeremiah gosh I
wouldn't want people to disapprove of me
why would anybody disapprove of what I'm
doing I'll tell you this when you start
going after your goals and you start
going after what it takes to make 20
sales and when you start doing the stuff
that it takes to actually create 5 10
$25,000 a month in a in your own
business you will experience everybody
does stuff that's going to try to pull
you back to where you came from to get
you to give up on your dream to get you
to quit
and I see it happen all the time with
people they make a commitment to start
something they make a commitment to get
started even getting mentored even
people that I meet that come to work
with me as far as this goes and listen I
will fight for you I will work with you
I will go to war with you and battle
with you to make sure that you get your
first 20 sales when you work with me but
if you don't show up answer my
calls ghost me and I don't hear from you
and then you write me 6 months later and
say that you're embarrassed of the fact
that you didn't show up and and that I
literally can't get a hold of you and
I've done everything and exhausted all
of my resources to be able to do
so that is like by the
way that's the reality of when it comes
to coaching some people literally just
cannot do what it takes what I'm looking
for is this I'm looking for people that
are willing to go after things that they
are willing to take risks that they are
willing to step out try some things out
test some stuff out and listen it
doesn't have to cost you a ton of money
to do so or time I only work 10 to 15
hours a week in my business I don't
think anybody needs to work more than
that even when they're
starting but here's what ends up
happening we end up challenging a lot of
our beliefs in our
mind you don't need to
invest more than a few hundred when it
comes to the technology and the tools
that you need to be able to build a
successful business
online now you might be asking at this
point in time okay Jeremiah just get to
the point already what is the best
product to
sell and I'm going to tell you
okay figure out how to take what you
know and this and by the way this comes
from working with thousands of
people in hundreds of different
niches Industries for the last 21
years and I can look at okay and this is
this is what people pay me for as I look
at at the Horizon of what industries are
out there right now and what is the
fastest way that you can increase your
income to5 to $25,000 a month with the
least amount of effort or upfront
investment for you and I can say
unequivocally it's when you
package and you bundle it together what
you
know right
you take your
knowledge you take what you
know combined with your
presence okay so what you know combined
with your
presence combined
with
support okay so what this is is you're
giving people access to your knowledge
access to you and access to in the
future if they get stuck knowing that
you're there to support them by the way
this is exactly what I offer to the
clients that we work with every single
day in their
businesses is the confidence that
they're going to get the
information on The Cutting Edge right
stuff to do at the right moment in time
not outdated information that that
worked 6 months ago that doesn't work
right now can I tell you
this stuff that worked 6 months ago
doesn't work anymore artificial
intelligence has almost completely
obsoleted itself when it comes to
marketing for most people and and listen
I was the first guy out there preaching
you got to use AI a year
ago people ignored it people who did it
made a a lot of money and then it
started to stop working again and now
we've literally pivoted away from people
are very resistant to AI they don't want
artificial intelligence created stuff
they want real connection as far as that
goes now we use AI to brainstorm stuff
and I and I and maybe I'll make another
video on how we brainstorm with AI and
how it can actually inspire you to go 10
20x with your
knowledge by inspiring you in a as a
research Arch assistant and a market
research assistant but I don't even use
AI anymore to create a lot of my
marketing and I'm even mentoring a lot
of my clients on moving away from using
Ai and how to use it as a research
assistant but not necessarily creating
everything for them and to inspire their
own mind to be able to work well and
then what people get access to is they
get access to me they get to work with
me personally I get to come alongside
them I'm I'm there making sure that
they're getting the job done I'm there
hounding them to see are you doing the
work and listen if they don't want that
I'll I'll back off it's whatever people
want I end up giving it to them as far
as that goes I've been doing this a
while and I know that not everybody is
the same they got different
personalities some people would rather
me be more hands off with them and they
just show me their work others would
rather that I'm a lot more handholding
but I offer that to people that I work
with and then the fure support to know
that maybe if they want to take a couple
months off or they get overwhelmed I'm
there to support them along the way to
even come back and encourage them to do
that even providing this to
people I still have people that tell me
you know Jeremiah it's just not the
right time it's not the right I don't
feel like I can do it as far as this
goes and that's why I say this I used to
not think this but now I I do 98% of
people are just not cut out to actually
build a
business they're not and maybe you're
watching this right now and you're
saying Jeremiah I don't think I'm cut
out for that can I encourage you on this
one you can become cut out for it I
realized that I was the 98% of people
that was not cut out for business 21
years ago that's why I worked for people
that were cut out to run companies build
companies and then I grew in my skill
set I started providing value I became
became CEO of these companies became the
decision maker but I still wasn't
risking my own money or reputation in
this and that's the part that is the
hardest for most people is when you go
out there to build your own business
you're risking your own reputation
you're risking your own finances your
own time and we end up taking that a lot
more seriously we end up holding on to
it a lot more tightly as far as that
goes and so what I would encourage you
is this
there's a lot of different business
models out there when it comes to making
the kind of finances that you want to
make that you could do if you can
package what you know give people access
to you and provide future support and
you can put that all together into a
monthly payment where people are
basically paying
you
monthly for this access whether they use
it or not that resource is there and you
price it you make your pricing very
competitive you price it just high
enough that it qualifies out people that
are going to waste your
time that's why what I offer it's it's
$200 a month for people to work with
me
minimum I literally you can't work with
me for less than $200 a month as far as
that
goes just
can't because I want to qualify out
anybody that that's too expensive as far
as that goes because what I found is
that for the people that that's too
expensive for they're not even going to
take advantage of
this they're not even going to do the
stuff that it
takes and you can literally figure that
out and that's where the second Factor
comes in in deciding how to price things
and what to
offer is focusing on the
impact and
result for your buyers okay so we may
have a desire to provide the best lowest
cost quality um not lowest quality right
highest quality product but the problem
is this is that people have an expected
perceived value based on price and I did
and I wish I knew this four years ago I
was selling a course it was actually
people would buy it and they would tell
me it was the world's best Facebook ads
course they ever bought by the way we
still have I believe the best Facebook
ads courses that are out there in our
program now the only way to access them
is by joining our
program but I was selling it for 47
bucks and people would and and and then
I would have people like schedule a call
with me and I would upgrade them to
one-on-one coaching I was maybe making
like a th000 to $2,000 a month at that
level
okay and and and and and it was it was a
struggle for me you might be like wait a
sec Jeremiah I thought you said you were
making a quar million dollars a year for
the last whatever okay tell me how this
story works out you're only making
$1,000 a month selling your coaching I
was doing services and Consulting for
companies that would pay me uh $8,000
$10,000 month retainers I had multiple
clients at that level retainer clients
where I was running their marketing so
for a time period when I was really
really struggling to sell my own courses
and coaching and memberships I had a
service-based business on the
side where I offered services and listen
I didn't cheap out on these Services
either I I I required people to pay me
what's was $8,000 a month
times 12 oh gosh the the math on this
one
$96,000 a year
okay so I was selling a
$96,000 a year package and by the way
most of these clients stayed with me for
a couple years these were not like one
and done wham bam thank you ma'am type
of things these were two to
threee contracts that we
had and I still have great relationship
with these people by the way I like if I
had one thing I can be proud
of today is that the people that paid me
$100,000 $200,000 a year for multiple
years in a row I am still friends with
them I can still literally call them up
for anything for for for like legitimate
like hey can you do me a favor could you
help me with this why because they made
way more than that during that time
period and and and I'll tell you this I
got I got a little bit of a little bit
of a pride for that one because there's
not a lot of people can who can say
that I can tell you that the people who
bought my $47 course they would tell me
repeatedly this is the best course we've
ever
bought and we still get that today we
have people who join my accelerator
program they're like Jeremiah you know I
I I I I'm in this program uh but maybe
right now it's not the best time for me
to do this but they always leave it with
this but you are literally the best and
and and and and you're what you your
information is the best and you're doing
a great work and and that's become my
reputation in the
marketplace is that we provide
legitimately the best
coaching the best
support for our clients and we will
continue to do that until the Lord takes
me home way off in the future right as
far as that goes okay I don't want to
get sentimental here as far as that goes
but just can I tell you this your
reputation matters when it comes to
business what your clients can say about
you but I'm going to tell you a flip
side to this
okay I have people to this day who tell
me that I am
unwise they call me a scammer they say
that I'm the worst person in the world
who are these people what do they have
like what evidence do they have for this
none they saw me on a Facebook ad and
they made a judgment about who I am
because of the things that I'm saying
there are people who watch videos of Me
on YouTube right now who leave those
comments never worked with me never done
business with me and then I got clients
who did business with me who are saying
that I'm literally the best at what it
takes so I'm going to tell you this you
could do all the right things
and you're not going to please everybody
you're going to have disappointment
disapproval people not liking you people
disliking you that are not worth your
time to think about I used to ruminate
and try to create a product that could
never have anybody say anything bad
about me that's why I priced this
incredible course at $47 and yet I still
got called a SC scammer for selling that
for 47 bucks and I
cried I'm I'm a little embarrassed to
say I cried over that but it was it was
it was it was hard for me I I was like
why are they calling me this because I
didn't realize how mean people could
be and I don't want to dwell on that but
I want to tell you this that one of the
number one things that you need to
develop if you're going to run a
business online is thick skin
there are mean people out there they're
going to say things about you that are
untrue these were
untruths and lies about me that people
were
saying and they didn't bother me because
maybe there was an iota of
truth but it's because I knew how much
this information helps
people and that people were unwilling to
even just give it a sh shot even with a
60-day money back guarantee unwilling to
try it out and so I I say all this to
encourage you you could literally do all
the right things have the highest level
of Integrity like like like we do and
still there will be people that will
disapprove of you as far as that goes
and so what I've had to learn
is to let go of all those opinions of
other people that are negative and to
really really focus on what are the ones
that are my cheerleaders that have my
back that are cheering me on that are
championing what we're doing what about
the companies that I built to over $20
million a year when I was working as CEO
of those
companies that I still can call to this
day and hang out with and talk to and we
friends with haven't destroyed the
relationship
that's what I focus on and so that's one
of the number one things that I want to
tell you is that you have to get your
mind right and you have to get your
thinking right if you want to make this
come together because what you believe
about
yourself
determines how much money you can make
in your own
business your level of
self-esteem and self-belief and learning
to not beat yourself up to not take on
what people say about
you and to learn to gas yourself up and
excite yourself and and light yourself
on fire literally that's what I that's
what I think of proverbially even
spiritually is every time that I go out
there I'm like pouring spiritual
gasoline on myself lighting myself on
fire to shine as brightly as
possible to share with you what's inside
of me and to bring that to the table and
that's what I hope that I've done just a
little bit of here
today what you have to do is you have to
package an offer these are offers right
here whether you're selling a $47 a
month by the way that's a really great
price point for a lot of people's
memberships $47 a month can even trial
it out at $27 a month we actually built
a membership for one of my clients his
name was Rick Pino and and he's an
incredible dude we built a business with
him that was a membership $27 a month
here over at worship coach.com where we
taught people how to write songs and and
and and and he had some of the top
worship leaders on here it was $27 a
month and we were making
$40,000 a month in Profit just off of
that one membership and his business
then went on to make over a million
dollar a month when we were working
together on
this now he he charges $97 a month for
it as far as this goes with a 14-day
trial okay so started at $27 a month
once things got refined the the the
courses started to grow the quality of
the product got better increase the
price to $97 a month as far as that goes
okay
and so when it comes
to whether your offer is $27 a month $47
a month or you're charging
96,2 200,000 a year for a service or a
package like that you have to make the
impact and the results your number one
priority and that's what a lot of people
get wrong and that's unfortunately why a
lot of people get scammed and that's why
a lot of people also don't feel
confident when it comes to selling and
offering their products and so that's
what I work with people on both through
my podcast as well as my coaching
program the client growth accelerator
that we have right here this is all
about how do you get those clients how
do you get those members how do you get
those subscribers and we're going to
accelerate You by mentoring you on how
to reach that six figure $10,000
$220,000 month level and even go to
seven figures with our training and
mentoring and coaching right here now
it's not available and open for you to
even register for but you can jump in on
our waiting list right here and when we
do open enrollment to it you can be the
first to know so you can find that over
at jeremi crow.com
accelerator um or you can click on one
of the links that are connected to my
site right here again I don't want to
make these videos be a sales pitch for
you but I want to tell you this that if
you want to work with us to help you put
together an offer that's going to create
consistent revenue for you that's going
to create the kind of income that you
want to have where we can show you how
to put together whether it be a
subscription or a course or a coaching
program or maybe you want to take an
e-commerce product and turn it into a
subscription or maybe you wanted to sell
a book and then monetize that book build
a personal brand we've helped a number
of different authors and speakers build
personal Brands out there with their
with their stuff here's there's a client
right now that we're working with right
now in my program she's working with a
few a few other people but she's just
the sweetest lady that you'll ever meet
her name is Mary she's one of our
clients in our accelerator program and
this is her right here she just launched
her book destined to shine right here
incredible and now we're working with
her to create a a backend product an
offer and course to be able to go deeper
with this and I I remember I followed
Mary's Journey she's she's just one of
the most amazing mentors that's out
there for people and and I remember when
I met her I was like listen like a book
might not be the best thing to start
with because it's not going to make you
the kind of money you want to make now
she's finding she launched her book
really fulfilled on this but it's not
bringing in the kind of cash flow that
she was expecting so but but it's
exciting because she's laid a lot of the
foundation for the results and the
impact and she knows what she wants to
charge money for and that's what we're
working with her now is why she joined
my accelerator program is to monetize
that to bring it right together to be
able to create some kind of an offer
that she can make a consistent income
with so that her or her husband don't
have to work a job and and can actually
go out there and have the impact that
they want to have on other people's
lives while providing value and
information to people and that's exactly
what I work with people to do every
single week is to take what they know
and their experiences and package it
into the highest impact for their
clients get the most results for their
clients and bring in the best cash flow
the right pricing for what their service
is okay so again I'd encourage you join
the waiting list for the accelerator
program you might also see some
different ads that we run for different
events and trainings that we do plug
into my podcast as well by the way we we
just brought this back I took a little
bit of a Hiatus on the podcast this week
beating writers block as a content
creator for good I'm excited for this
lesson as far as this goes and of course
subscribe to this YouTube channel we're
going to be providing training videos
every single week with you here's what I
want to encourage you if you're watching
this leave me a comment below this video
and let me know what you would like me
to teach what you would like me to
unpack what you would like me to share
to go deeper with you as far as future
videos that we create on this YouTube
channel I want you to be the one that
inspires what we create as far as this
goes and I want this to be interactive
this video was actually the result of
something that somebody had said and
shared that they wanted me to teach and
share as far as that goes and here we
are today with this video okay so leave
a comment below let us know what you'd
like us to share and get on the waiting
list for the accelerator when we open
those doors we'd love to have you in
there with us to work with you even if
it's just to just to try it out for for
a month to see if it's a good fit for
you as of this recording right now we
may change it in the future so don't
hold me to it we actually do provide a a
30-day money back guarantee to try out
the program just to see if it's a good
fit for you here's the cool thing almost
nobody ever takes us up on the 30 days
because they're like okay this was the
best this is amazing I'm thankful to be
here and and and I'm going to stay in
here and a lot of our clients stay for
for years as far as that goes in our
program not because they you
know they're they're struggling but
because they're growing and continuing
to grow and seeing the changes and
results week after week after week and
they have access to the support and me
to be able to come alongside them when
they're struggling to say okay here's
where we need to Pivot here's where we
need to course correct here's what needs
to be adjusted here are some of the
adjustments that need to be made and
then they're Off to the Races as far as
that goes all right thank you and we'll
see you on the next video we'll talk
soon